>> Brian Holt: 我敢说你永远不会用这个。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I will venture to say
that you will never use this one.
这主要是供图书馆作者使用的。
This is mostly for library authors.
我只想让你知道它在外面
I just want to let you
know that it's out there.
我告诉过你，数据只流一个，反应是从父母到
I've told you that data only flows one
way, in react it goes from parent to
孩子，然后那个孩子，孩子和孩子，对吧 ?
child, and then that child to that child,
and child to child, right?
所以它只会向下移动，不会后退。
So it only moves down,
it doesn't go back up.
这就是你把它翻到它头上的方式
This is how you flip it on it's head.
实际上，您可以让子代控制父代。
You can actually have
a child control the parent.
我这里有西雅图，华盛顿，如果我要删除
So here I have from that I have Seattle,
Washington and if I delete and
单击验证表单，使其成为红色，然后重新聚焦在该表单上，对。
click validate form it'll make that
red and then refocus on it, right.
所以我在这里有一个精心设计的输入，然后我就需要集中精力在这个问题上。
So I have an elaborate input here and then
I need to be able to focus on that right.
这就是父母会做的事对吧
Which is something that
the parent would do, right?
所以这实际上允许孩子向父母展示一个功能
So this is actually allowing the child
to expose a function to the parent so
家长可以说嘿，关注这个，对吧 ?
the parent can say hey,
focus on this, right?
这就是用它来处理的事情。
So that's what this is doing
here with useImperativeHandle.
我在这里不太了解细节因为这只是
I'm not gonna get too much into the weeds
of the details here because it's just
没那么有趣
not that interesting.
但欢迎您通过此代码进行挖掘
But you're welcome to dig
in through this code and
如果这对你有用的话就更多了
figure out more of what it
does if this is useful to you.
这就是在做什么呢 ?
So what this is doing,
this useImperativeHandle,
就是把这个功能回归到这个叫做焦点的功能上。
is it's returning this
function here called focus.
现在家长电话的重点放在这个精心设计的输入上，对吧 ?
And now the parent call focus
on this elaborate input, right?
然后我用这个向前引用的功能来做
And then I'm doing that with
this forwardRef function,
基本上是说如果有人对我做了裁判
which is basically saying, hey,
if someone makes a ref on me
我要在这个特定项目上提供功能，对吧 ?
I'm going to make functions available
on this particular item, right?
所以现在如果我在这里发现我有个城市艾尔和一个国家
So now if I go down here, notice that
I have a cityEl and a stateEl and
我正在用这俩人的裁判
I'm using ref on both of those.
然后，如果我在这里，他们在这里有一个国家厄尔尼诺和城市的引用，对吧 ?
And then if I go down in here, they have
a ref here of stateEl, and cityEl, right?
然后我就有了这个验证功能
And then I have here this
validation function which is
我在 Stack Overflow [LAUGH]上发现了它。
law I found it on Stack Overflow [LAUGH].
这将验证城市，这将验证状态。
This will validate a city and
this will validate a state.
所以如果这个城市是无效的，对，就会说cityEl.current.焦距，对吧 ?
So if the city is not valid, right, then
it'll say cityEl.current.focus, right?
这个聚焦功能来自这里。
And that focus function came from here.
所以，我真的不认为你会写太多这些。
So again, I really don't think you'll
be writing very many of these.
但很多图书馆的作者将会为
But a lot of library authors
will be writing these things for
你， >> Brian Holt: 有道理吗 ?
you,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Make sense?
同一件事
Same thing here.
如果我将其删除，然后在此处放置 S ，然后单击验证表单。
If I delete this, and you put S here and
then click validate form.
它会聚焦在那个上面，让它真正地捕捉到它的焦点。
It'll focus on that one so that it'll
actually capture the focus there.
>> Brian Holt: 这就是你所拥有的所有挂钩。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And that's it,
that is all of the hooks that you have.
没有更多的了。
There are no more.
还有一个，但是我觉得他们把它删了，因为它太乱了。
There was like one more, but I think they
deleted it because it was so confusing.
这些都不是令人困惑的。
These are the not confusing ones.